Guide to the Gray Thoron papers, 1922-1987.
Thoron, Gray papers, 1922-1987
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Gray Thoron papers, 1922-1987.
18-1-1695
Thorn, Gray.
18.3 cubic ft.
Correspondence, surveys, memoranda, applications, reports, announcements, financial records, and other materials.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Files of Gray Thoron include correspondence, surveys, memoranda, applications, reports, announcements, and other materials pertaining to Cornell Law School admissions, students, curricula, and examinations; personnel recruitment information and applications; budgets, endowments, fundraising, scholarships, and fellowships; alumni; the International Legal Studies Program; academic freedom and tenure; faculty members; policies; and other papers relating to Thoron's position as Law School dean.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Before teaching law at Cornell University, Gray Thoron engaged in private law practice and was Assistant to the Solicitor General of the United States Department of Justice. He later joined the Cornell faculty, and from 1956 to 1963 was Dean of the Law School. His field of teaching and research includes criminal law, procedure (criminal and civil), professional ethics, and practice. He has participated in many national programs, in the activities of Bar Associations; in educational programs at Universities, including Texas, Michigan, and the Salzburg Seminar in American Studies. He served on the Overseers Committee to the Harvard Law School from 1960-1966. He is a Fellow of the American Bar Foundation and a member of the New York State Bar Association's Committee on State Constitutional Revision and the Association of American Law Schools' Committee on Academic Freedom and Tenure.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Files of Gray Thoron include correspondence, surveys, memoranda, applications, reports, announcements, and other materials pertaining to Cornell Law School admissions, students, curricula, and examinations; personnel recruitment information and applications; budgets, endowments, fundraising, scholarships, and fellowships; alumni; the International Legal Studies Program; academic freedom and tenure; faculty members; policies; and other papers relating to Thoron's position as Law School dean.
Also, correspondence of previous deans, including Robert S. Stevens, William H. Farnham, George C. Bogert, and Charles K. Burdick. Also included are papers concerning Thoron's involvement with various organizations, conventions and committees, including the American Law Student Association, the American Bar Association (including admission to the bar and exam questions),
State Bar Associations, the New York State Constitutional Convention, the Association of American Law Schools, and the Lawyers Committee for Civil Rights Under Law.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Thoron, Gray.; Bogert, George C.; Stevens, Robert S.; American Bar Association.; American Law Student Association.; Association of American Law Schools.; Cornell Law School--Admission.; Cornell Law School--Alumni.; Cornell Law School--Curricula.; Cornell Law School--Endowments.; Cornell Law School--Entrance requirements.; Cornell Law School--Examinations.; Cornell Law School--Faculty.; Cornell Law School--Finance.; Cornell Law School--Funds and scholarships.; Cornell Law School--Graduate students.; Cornell Law School--Students.; Cornell Law School.; Cornell Law School. International Legal Studies Program.
Subjects:
Academic freedom--United States.; Constitutional conventions--New York (State).; Law--Study and teaching--United States.; Law examinations--United States.; Law students--United States.; College teachers--United States.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of the archivist.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Subject files
  All the material in the collection may not be covered by this guide.
- CLS - Dean's Reports 1950-1956, 1951-1956 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- CLS - Dean's Reports 1945-1950, 1946-1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- CLS - Dean's Reports 1940-1945, 1941-1945 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Gannet Project in Libel Law, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- CLS - Budget Matters 1934-1937, 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- CLS - Replacement - 1947-1955 - Unsuccessful Negotiations, 1937-1953 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- ALSA Student Bar Award Competition 1956 The Cornell Law Student Association, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- CLS - Replacements - 1946-1949 Active Correspondence, 1946-1949 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- CLS - Replacements - 1950-1952 Active Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- CLS - Replacements - 1946-1949 Misc. Correspondence, 1946-1949 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- CLS - Replacements - 1950-1952 Misc. Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- CLS - Replacements - 1947-1950 Int. & Comp. Law, 1947-1952 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- CLS - Replacement Possibilities (Monkmeyer, Herbert N.), 1947-1949 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- CLS - Replacements - 1953-1955 Active Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- CLS - Replacements - 1953-1956 Misc. Correspondence, 1953-1956 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Faculty Applications, 1951-1956 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- International Law Program 1951- Rothstein Prize, 1951-1956 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- III. Bar Review Survey Admission to the Bar, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- II. Bar Review Survey Admission to the Bar, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- I. Bar Review Survey Admission to the Bar, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- California Admission to the Bar, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Connecticut Admission to the Bar, 1950-1953 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Hawaii Admission to the Bar, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Nevada Admission to the Bar, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- New Jersey Admission to the Bar, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- II. New York - Correspondence Admission to the Bar, 1936-1956 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- I. New York - Correspondence Admission to the Bar, 1928-1941 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- New York Joint Conference on Legal Education - Admission to the Bar, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- New York - Miscellaneous Admission to the Bar, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- New York - Results of Bar Examination Admission to the Bar, 1938-1956 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- North Carolina Admission to the Bar, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Dean's Report to Alumni Affairs, 1941, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- American Association for the Comparative Study of Law, 1951-1955 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- American Bar Association Journal; American Bar Association, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Junior Bar Conference; American Bar Association, 1948-1950 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- II. Legal Education & Admission to the Bar (Section of) American Bar Association, 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- I. Legal Education & Admission to the Bar (Section on) American Bar Association, 1945-1953 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Miscellaneous; American Bar Association, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- American Bar Association Loan Program, 1964-1969 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- American Bar Foundation "Little Green Book", 1957-1963 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Review of Legal Education; American Bar Association, 1951-1956 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- II. Survey of Legal Profession; American Bar Association, 1949-1954 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- I. Survey of Legal Profession; American Bar Association, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Annual Meetings; Association of American Law Schools, 1944-1948 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Articles of Association; Association of American Law Schools, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Correspondence, Miscellaneous; Association of American Law Schools, 1943-1946 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Inspection by, 1957; Association of American Law Schools, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Legal Education and the War, Committee on; Association of American Law Schools, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Legal Literature, etc., in the Armed Forces Committee on; Association of American Law Schools, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Miscellaneous; Association of American Law Schools, 1946-1957 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Pre-Legal Education, Committee on; Association of American Law Schools, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Racial Discrimination, Special Committee on; Association of American Law Schools, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Registry of Research Projects; Association of American Law Schools, 1955-1958 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Social Sciences, Committee on Readings in the; Association of American Law Schools, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Teaching and Examination Methods, Committee on; Association of American Law Schools, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Announcements, Law School, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Arts and Sciences, College of, 1943-1957 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Board of Regents, New York, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Business and Public Administration, School of, 1954-1957 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Civil Defense, Myron Taylor Hall, 1950-1955 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Civil Liberties Research Centers, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Requests for Attorney, 1952-1958 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Cooperative Law Course, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Business-Law Combined-Degree Programs, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Engineering-Law Combined-Degree Programs, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Cornell Daily Sun, 1928-1043 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Cornell Law Association, 1931-1947 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Review, 1958-1961 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous Cornell Law Quarterly, 1944-1961 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Building and Grounds Cornell University, 1945-1957 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- II. Deans of the Faculty, Cornell, 1941-1946 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- I. Dean of the Faculty, Cornell, 1933-1941 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- II. Development-Corporation Information - Cornell University, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- I. Development-Corporation Information - Cornell University, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Economic Status of the Faculty, Committee on; Cornell University, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Emeritus Professors, Appointment of; Cornell University, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Graduate School, Cornell University, 1928-1954 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Interfaculty Relations, Committee on; Cornell University, 1951-1952 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Military Service, Committee on; Cornell University, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Provost, Committee on Appointment of; Cornell University, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Public Information, Office of; Cornell University, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- II. President, Cornell University, 1942-1943 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- I. President, Cornell University, 1944-1950 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- I. Registrar, Cornell University, 1929-1952 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- II. Registrar, Cornell University, 1953-1955 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- III. Registrar, Cornell University, 1956-1958 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Safety Division, Cornell University, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Secretary, Cornell University, 1937-1950 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Size of the University, Committee on; Cornell University, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Student Conduct Committee; Cornell University, 1948-1955 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Treasurer, Cornell University, 1931-1955 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- I. President, Cornell University, 1931-1941 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Degrees Awarded, 1942-1950 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Graduate and Special Students, 1952-1955 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- "Higher Education and National Affairs", 1956 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Industrial and Labor Relations, School of, 1951-1957 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Institutes and Conferences, 1951-1957 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Inter-American Academy of Comparative and International Law, Undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Domicile of Students, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Etching of Myron Taylor Hall, 1952-1954 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Miscellaneous, Examinations, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Practice Examination; Examinations, 1954-1958 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Advisors; Faculty, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Bulletin Board; Faculty, 1956-1967 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Exchange Opportunities, Fellowships; Faculty, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Executive Committee; Faculty, 1931-1958 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Grading; Faculty, 1947-1954 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Miscellaneous; Faculty, 1949-1957 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Fellowships, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- V. Stevens, Dean Robert S. Correspondence, 1954-1956 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- VI. Stevens, Dean Robert S. Correspondence, 1951-1953 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- III. Stevens, Dean Robert S. Correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- II. Stevens, Dean Robert S. Correspondence, 1940-1948 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- I. Stevens, Robert S. Correspondence, 1925-1939 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Farnham, Acting Dean William H. Correspondence, 1928-1951 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Administration Committee Correspondence, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Secretary Correspondence, 1928-1958 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Curriculum Three-Year Course, 1923-1924 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Curriculum Miscellaneous, 1922-1946 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Bogert, Dean George C. Correspondence, 1923-1925 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- III. Burdick, Dean Charles K. Correspondence, 1933-1942 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- II. Burdick, Dean Charles K. Correspondence, 1929-1933 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- I. Burdick, Dean Charles K. Correspondence, 1923-1928 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Employees; International Legal Studies Program, 1947-1956 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous; International Legal Studies Program, 1949-1951 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Prospectus, Ford Foundation; International Legal Studies Program, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Students: International Legal Studies Program, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Introduction of the Study of Law, Cases and Materials, 1953-1956 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Ivy League Law Schools Conference, 1941-1945 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Jennings Fund; Law Library, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous; Law Library, 1935-1950 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Reports; Law Library, 1942-1945 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- II. Legal Aid (see 3-50), 1948-1950 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Irvine Lectureship; Lectureships, 1931-1956 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- II. Memoranda to Students, 1955-1957 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- I. Memoranda to Students, 1953-1955 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- CLS - Gifts - Wanderlich Prize, 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Thaine, Katherine E.; Personnel, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Memoranda; Personnel, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Payroll; Personnel, Undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Robert Slater Co.; Prizes, 1955-1959 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Miscellaneous; Prizes, 1924-1957 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Real Property Prize; Prizes, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Consolidated Laws Service; Prizes, 1952-1955 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- II. Woodruff, Edwin H.; Professorships, 1947-1955 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- I. Woodruff, Edwin H.; Professorships, 1927-1947 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- White, J. DuPratt Professorship; Professorships, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- III. Woodruff, Edwin H., Professorships, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Cromwell, Wm. Nelson; Professorships, Undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
- McRoberts Professorships; Professorships, 1938-1954 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Bostwick, Charles D. Law Scholarship; Scholarships, 1953-1956 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Burdick, Charles K. Scholarship, Scholarships, 1949-1952 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- II. Burdick, Charles K. Scholarship; Scholarships, 1945-1947 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- I. Burdick, Charles K. Scholarship; Scholarships, 1947-1949 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Dalley, Francis Kay Fund, Scholarship; Scholarships, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Dorset Scholarship; Scholarships, 1950-1953 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Ellenbogen, Franklyn Jr., Memorial Scholarship; Scholarships, 1953-1968 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Frazer Scholarship; Scholarships, 1926-1947 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Hoyt, George W. Fund Scholarship; Scholarships, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Knott, Dickson Randolph Memorial Scholarship; Scholarships, 1943-1962 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- I. Legal Aid, 1938-1948 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Liberian Program Lectureships, 1945-1954 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Milliman, Leonard T. Co-operative Law Scholarship; Scholarships, 1946-1962 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Pitt, Melvin I. Scholarship; Scholarships, 1952-1955 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- II. Pound Scholarship; Scholarships, 1935-1938 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- I. Pound Scholarship; Scholarships, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Sackett, Henry W. Scholarship; Scholarships, 1931-1951 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Taylor, Harry L., "Anonymous Fund" Scholarship; Scholarships, 1950-1955 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Van Cleef, Mynderse Scholarship; Scholarship, 1926-1932 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Tompkins County Trust Company Endowment in Honor of William H. Burns, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Whiteside, Horace Eugene Memorial Scholarship; Scholarship, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Williver Memorial Fund Scholarship; Scholarships, 1938-1939 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Wilson, Lyman P. Memorial Fund; Scholarships, 1951-1954 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Woodruff Scholarship; Scholarships, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Scribes, 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous; Scholarships, 1925-1958 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- State Education Department, 1928-1956 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Statistics for Faculty Meetings 1955-1956, 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Statistics for Faculty Meetings 1956-1957, 1953-1957 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Statistics for Faculty Meetings 1954-1955, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Statistics for Faculty Meetings 1953-1954, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Statistics for Faculty Meetings 1951-1952, 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Statistics for Faculty Meetings 1952-1953, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Statistics for Faculty Meetings 1950-1951, 1948-1952 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Statistics for Faculty Meetings 1949-1950, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Statistics for Faculty Meetings 1948-1949, 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Statistics for Faculty Meetings 1937-1938, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- American Law Student Association; Student Affairs, 1949-1956 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Coif, Order of; Student Affairs, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Delta Theta Phi; Student Affairs, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Forum; Student Affairs, 1950-1957 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Honor System; Student Affairs, 1947-1956 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Housing; Student Affairs, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Law Student Association; Student Affairs, 1948-1957 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Miscellaneous; Student Affairs, 1949-1952 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Moot Court; Student Affairs, 1949-1957 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Phi Alpha Delta; Student Affairs, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Phi Kappa Phi; Student Affairs, 1947-1969 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Summer Sessions Cornell University, 1923-1959 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Summer Sessions at Other Law Schools, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Rota; Student Affairs, 1949-1952 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Statistics for Faculty Meetings 1947-1948, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Teaching Assignments, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Visitors to Law School, 1946-1956 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Washington School of Public Law, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- CLS - Law School Council - Membership Lists and Agendas - 1958-1962, 1958-1962 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- CLS - Admissions Reports 1948-1963, 1957-1962 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- CLS - Publicity 1956-, 1957-1960 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- CLS - Council - Memberships, Invitations, Acceptances, etc., 1959-1961 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- CLS - Council - 1959 Meeting, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- CLS - Annual Giving - 1956-57 Campaign, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Cornell Law School - Annual Giving; Area Chairman Letters 1956, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- CLS - Annual Giving - Area Lists, Undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
- CLS - Gift Reports 1957-1962, 1957-1962 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- CLS - Bar Exam - New York Statistics and Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- CLS - Annual Giving - 1958-1959 Campaign Thank-You Letters, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- CLS - Annual Giving - Area Chairman Letters - 1957, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- CLS - 1957-58 Campaign, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- CLS - Annual Giving - 1957 Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- CLS Annual Giving - Day Hall Copies - 1959, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- CLS - Annual Giving - Day Hall Letters 1959-60, 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- CLS - Annual Giving - 1959 Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- CLS - Annual Giving - 1958-59 Campaign, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- CLS - Annual Giving - Area Chairmen 1958-1959, 1957-1959 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- CLS - Annual Giving - 1958 Reports, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Proj. - CLS - Myron Taylor Hall, 1957-1959 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Thompson, George J., 1952-1957 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Ward, Peter, 1951-1959 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Warren, Ernest N., 1956-1961 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Business Law 150, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- (Untitled Replacements Committee), 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- CLS - Annual Giving - 1960-1961 Thank-you letters, etc., 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- CLS - Annual Giving - 1960-1961 Reports, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- CLS - Annual Giving - 1960-61 Misc., 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- CLS - Annual Giving - 1959-60 Campaign, 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- CLS - Annual Giving - Area Chairmen 1959-60, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- CLS - Annual Giving - 1959-60 Thank-you letters, 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Rubery, Paul T., 1956 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Schlesinger, Rudolf B., 1950-1961 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Sneed, Joseph T., 1956-1960 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Stevens, Dean Robert s., 1948-1959 (Box 5, Folder 23)